All right.
Lab culture.
Death and destruction.
I can just film you all the time.
Don't film me, though.
It's a tool to be used like
it says in the scriptures
we're supposed to be things
that act and not to be
acted upon If we start using
AI too much then AI starts
using us and that should
be the other way around
it taught me how to make the
threads pretty well that's
pretty good it's funny how
bad AI's spatial reasoning
is it really has no concept
of like 3D space at all
— it makes sense because
it's just an algorithm
AI is not our equal.
No.
It is our tool.
is it telling me what to
do or am I telling it what
to do you know is it acting
upon me or am I acting
upon it because